Finding Aid for the S.A. Griffin collection of underground poetry, Scott Wannberg, and The Carma Bums LSC.2248
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Writings collected by Griffin (Box 23, Box 24, Box 25, Box 26, Box 27, Box 28, Box 29, Box 30, Box 31, Box 32, Box 33, Box 34, Box 35, Box 36, Box 37, Box 38, Box 39, Box 40, Box 41, Box 42, Box 43, Box 44, Box 45, Box 46, Box 47, Box 48, Box 49, Box 50, Box 51, Box 52, Box 53, Box 54, Box 55, Box
  - Serials (Box 343, Box 344, Box 345, Box 116, Box 117, Box 118, Box 119, Box 120, Box 121, Box 122, Box 123, Box 124, Box 125, Box 126, Box 127, Box 128, Box 129, Box 130, Box 131, Box 132, Box 133, Box 134, Box 135, Box 136, Box 137, Box 138, Box 139, Box 140, Box 141, Box 142, Box 143, Box 144,
    - Henry Moore at Thomas Gibson Fine Art Ltd. London., circa 1986 (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - Here Doesn't Come The Flying Fuck! Sunland., undated (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - High Times, no. 340. New York., 2003 December (Box 129, Folder 3)
      This issue features an interview with musician/composer/author Dave Amram.
    - Highwire Daze, no. 58. Burbank., 1998 June/July (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - Hip Magazine, no. 1. Los Angeles., undated (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - Ho, no. 0. Los Angeles., 1991 August (Box 193, Folder 6)
    - Ho!, no. 1. Los Angeles., 1993 (Box 129, Folder 6)
      This comix publication edited by Marcel DeJure features the work of Onyx regulars and includes "What's Going On!" by Josue Menjivar, Bill O'Mahoney's interview with Beck, "Xenopata" by Gash, and back cover illustration by Mark Durham.
    - Ho!, no. 2. Los Angeles., 1993 Fall (Box 129, Folder 6)
      This issue is the Super-Ultra-Mega-Special Heavy Metal Edition.
    - Ho!, no. 4. Los Angeles., 1999 (Box 129, Folder 6)
      This issue includes work by the following artists: Nora Keyes, Dame Darcy, Camille Rose Garcia, Amos, Mark Gash, and Mark Durham.
    - lahoja, no. 1. Los Angeles., 1991 December (Box 193, Folder 6)
    - The Hollywood Kids Street Gossip, v. 2, no. 26. Los Angeles., 1985 (Box 129, Folder 7)
      This issue presents "it's flaming!" in honor of the publication's 1 and 1/2 year birthday. An advertisement for Griffin's BOSS show appears in this issue.
    - The Hollywood Kids Street Gossip, v. 2, no. 26. Los Angeles., 1985 (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - The Hollywood Star Magazine, v. 1, no. 1. Los Angeles., 1979 (Box 129, Folder 8)
      This magazine features a story on Elvis Presley's bisexuality and Charles Manson's discussion about sex cult celebrities.
    - The Holy eARTh, Santa Cruz., 1982 (Box 346)
    - Homeless Writers Forum, v. 2. Los Angeles., 1994 October (Box 129, Folder 9)
    - Homeless Writers Forum. Los Angeles., 1995 Spring (Box 129, Folder 9)
    - Homeless Writers Forum. Los Angeles., 1996 (Box 129, Folder 9)
    - The Hooligan. Denver., 1999 (Box 129, Folder 10)
      This issue features Skye Barker's interview with Steve Wilson.
    - Honk If Yer Horny, v. 3, no. 69. Hollywood., 1992 (Box 129, Folder 11)
      This issue features photos of the band by Jeffoto and lyrics by Canya Fuck'er (Pleasant Gehman) and other band members to songs such as "Oh My Darlin' 69" and "Everybody's Fuckin' My Baby."
    - Honk If Yer Horny: A Touch of Class. Hollywood., 1994-1995 (Box 129, Folder 11)
      This is a fifteen month triple XXX rated pin-up calendar which includes "country music without the o" history for almost every day of each month. All photos by Jeffoto. Text and layout by Pleasant Gehman.
    - Horseshit, no. 1. Hermosa Beach., 1965 (Box 129, Folder 12)
    - Horseshit, no. 2. Hermosa Beach., 1967 (Box 129, Folder 12)
    - Horseshit, no. 3. Hermosa Beach., 1968 (Box 129, Folder 12)
    - Horseshit, no. 4. Hermosa Beach., 1970 (Box 129, Folder 12)
    - Hot City. West Hollywood., 1996 Fall (Box 129, Folder 13)
    - Huckster's Pitch, no. 1. Los Angeles., circa 1985 (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - Humble Propaganda. Reseda., circa 1999 (Box 129, Folder 14)
      This issue features an interview with Henry Rollins.
    - Hup, no. 1. San Francisco., 1987 (Box 129, Folder 15)
      Art and stories by R. Crumb.
    - Hup, no. 2. San Francisco., 1987 (Box 129, Folder 15)
    - Hustler, v. 3, no. 6. Columbus., 1976 December (Box 129, Folder 16)
      This issue features an interview with Charles Bukowski.
    - Image, v. 13, no. 1-2. St. Louis., 1985 (Box 129, Folder 17)
    - The Inch. Sacramento., 2007 November (Box 129, Folder 18)
      This is a little magazine associated with the Poems-For-All series. This issue features Phil Goldvarg: Zapatista Poet and includes a tribute to Queen of Bohemia, Philomene Long (1940-2007).
    - I Want A Poem To Be Hard Like A Bullet. Fort Worth., 1992 (Box 130, Folder 1)
      This is a Todd Moore fanzine by Robert W. Howington.
    - In Remembrance. Studio City., 1987 (Box 130, Folder 2)
      According to Editor Jenny Soup, this publication is a grave collection of poetry, collage, and reviews.
    - In Remembrance, no. 6. Studio City., undated (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - In Remembrance, no. 7. Studio City., undated (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - Infinite Degree of Freedom, no. 2. Denver., 1989 (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - Inkshed, no. 20. Hull., 1991 Spring (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - Insomnia, v. 2, no. 1. Whittier., 1993 Winter (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - Insomnia, v. 2, no. 2. Whittier., 1993 Spring (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - Insomnia, v. 2, no. 3. Whittier., 1993 Summer (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - Insomnia, v. 3, no. 2. Whittier., 1994 Spring (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - Insomnia, v. 3, no. 3. Whittier., 1994 Summer (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - Insomnia, v. 4, no. 1. Whittier., 1995 Spring (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - Instant Classics, v. 1. New York., 1989 (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - Instant Pussy, no. 4. Albuquerque., 2006 March (Box 130, Folder 7)
      This zine by Misti Rainwater-Lites combines porn and poetry. In her letter from the editor she writes, "This issue contains a poem about a punk rock guy (Mr. Spent Meat) getting sucked off by Courtney Love. It doesn't get much more exciting than that."
    - Instant Pussy, no. 12. Albuquerque., 2006 December (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - InterBang, v. 1, no. 3. Los Angeles., 1996 February (Box 130, Folder 8)
    - InterBang, no. 7. Venice., 1998 Summer (Box 130, Folder 8)
    - Intimate Apparel. Oakland., 1990 (Box 130, Folder 9)
      The Figurative Art of Beatrice Wood catalogue.
    - Invisible City, no. 3. San Francisco., 1983 (Box 130, Folder 10)
      This publication features writing from Robert Crosson, John Thomas, and Paul Vangelisti.
    - Io, no. 2. Cape Elizabeth., 1971 (Box 343, Folder 6)
      This is a reprint of an issue originally published in Amherst in 1966.
    - Itchy & Scratchy Comics, no. 1. Los Angeles., 1993 (Box 130, Folder 11)
    - The Ja Ja Circle. Denver., 2001 April (Box 130, Folder 12)
      This Marija Cerjak Society Flesh Poetics magazine published by Motchka Press documents the Underground 2001.
    - The Jacaranda Review, v. 3, no. 2. Denver., 1988 Fall/Winter (Box 130, Folder 13)
      This publication, funded by the Graduate Students Association and the Department of English at the University of California, Los Angeles, includes an extensive L.A. Poetry Supplement.
    - The Jackleg, v. 1. Los Angeles., 1995 (Box 130, Folder 14)
    - Ja'p, v. 1, no. 1. Los Angeles., 1987 October/November (Box 130, Folder 15)
      This Journal of Quantum 'Pataphysics is edited and published by Nigey Lennon and the Los Angeles Institute of Quantum 'Pataphysics.
    - Joseph Stella. Washington, D.C., 1990 Fall (Box 131, Folder 1)
      This Joseph Stella: Paintings and Works on Paper catalog is published by the Pensler Galleries.
    - Journal For The Protection Of All Beings, no. 1. San Francisco., 1961 (Box 131, Folder 2)
      This "Love-Shot" issue is edited and signed by Michael McClure, Lawrence Ferlinghetti, and David Meltzer.
    - Journal For The Protection Of All Beings, no. 2. San Francisco., 1968 (Box 131, Folder 2)
      This "On The Barricades: Revolution & Repression" issue was published on Bastille Day.
    - Jóvenes en Resistencia zines. Los Angeles., circa 2013 (Box 343, Folder 7)
    - Kamini Press Catalogue. Stockholm., 2012 January (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - The Kerouac Connection, no. 30. Menlo Park., 2000 Fall (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - The Kerouac Rag, no. 1. Torquay., 1999-2000 Winter (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - Key-Z Productions Catalog. Eugene., 1998 (Box 131, Folder 6)
      Key-Z Productions is dedicated to the work of Ken Kesey and the Merry Band of Pranksters.
    - Key-Z Productions Catalog. Eugene., 1999 (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - Kill Poet broadsides. San Diego., undated (Box 131, Folder 7)
      This folder contains a series of signed Viva La Poem broadsides for the following writers: Cat Benitez, Amelie Florence, Elly Portnoy, Brad Burjan, David Smith, Kalamity J, Jason Neese, and Jamie Neese.
    - Kombat. Indianapolis., 1995 Fall (Box 131, Folder 8)
    - The Kyoto Review, no. 7. Kyoto., 1976 Spring (Box 131, Folder 9)
    - L.A. Driver, v. 1, no. 2. North Hollywood., 1989 Fall (Box 131, Folder 10)
    - L.A. Driver, v. 3, no. 1. North Hollywood., 1991-1992 Winter Solstice (Box 131, Folder 10)
    - L.A. Star. Los Angeles., 1992 March (Box 131, Folder 11)
      This unauthorized newspaper features Justice Howard on its cover and includes an interview with Llana Lloyd, "Glitter Goddess" of the Sunset Strip.
    - L.A. Weekly, v.11, no. 32. Los Angeles., 1989 July 14-20 (Box 193, Folder 10)
    - L.A. Weekly, v.16, no. 32. Los Angeles., 1996 July 5-11 (Box 153, Folder 4)
      This issue features the "found" Bukowski poems.
    - L.A. Weekly, v. 30, no. 51. Los Angeles., 2008 November 7-13 (Box 193, Folder 10)
    - Laguna Poets Series, no. 81. Laguna Beach., 1998 (Box 131, Folder 12)
      This issue features Rick Lupert's Lizard King of the Laundromat and is inscribed to Griffin by Lupert.
    - Laguna Poets Series, no. 122. Laguna Beach., 1999 (Box 131, Folder 12)
      This issue features Doug Knott's Holding Pattern and is inscribed to Griffin by Knott.
    - Laguna Poets Series, no. 207. Laguna Beach., 2001 (Box 131, Folder 12)
      This issue features Paul Suntup's A Boy and His Blowtorch and is inscribed to Griffin by Suntup.
    - Lame Brain, v. 1, no. 5. Chicago., 1986 October (Box 131, Folder 13)
    - Left Bank Distribution Catalog. Seattle., 1997 (Box 131, Folder 14)
    - Lemon Fingers Emerge, no. 2. Long Beach., undated (Box 131, Folder 15)
      This is a collection of Los Angeles area poetry.
    - Lemon Fingers Emerge, no. 3. Long Beach., undated (Box 131, Folder 15)
    - Leon Golub -- New Paintings Catalog. New York., 1963 (Box 131, Folder 16)
      This catalog is from Golub's exhibition at the Allan Frumkin Gallery.
    - Letra Nova. Anaheim., 1994 (Box 131, Folder 17)
    - Letra Nova, no. 5. Anaheim., 1995 May-June (Box 131, Folder 17)
    - The Liar, no. 6. North Vancouver., 1990 (Box 131, Folder 18)
    - LIFE, v. 47, no. 12. Chicago., 1959 September 21 (Box 153, Folder 5)
      This issue features "Squaresville U.S.A. vs. Beatsville" on the Venice West scene.
    - Live Wild Or Die! Portland., circa 1989 (Box 131, Folder 19)
    - Living Batch News. Albuquerque., circa 1989 (Box 131, Folder 20)
      This newsletter for the Living Batch Bookstore includes a preview for The Carma Bums, No Seat Belts Tour of Words in store show on August 24th with Ellyn Maybe, S.A. Griffin, Mike Bruner, Doug Knott, Bobbo Staron, and Scott Wannberg. This folder also contains two Living Batch Bookstore bookmarks.
    - Loca, no. 11. Monterey Park., circa 1989 (Box 131, Folder 21)
      This magazine was created by Queen Felicia Dominguez and Princess Gwynne Garfinkle.
    - Los. Los Angeles., 1992 April (Box 131, Folder 22)
    - Los. Los Angeles., 1992 June (Box 131, Folder 23)
    - Los. Los Angeles., 1993 June (Box 131, Folder 23)
    - Los. Los Angeles., 1993 November (Box 131, Folder 23)
    - Los. Los Angeles., 1994 Spring (Box 131, Folder 23)
    - Los. Los Angeles., 1998 Winter (Box 131, Folder 23)
    - Los Angeles. Los Angeles., 1993 October (Box 131, Folder 24)
      This issue features a story on the pulse of Beat culture in present day Los Angeles.
    - Los Angeles 1956. Los Angeles., circa 1990 (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Los Angeles Independent, v. 66, no. 16. Los Angeles., 1998 October 21 (Box 132, Folder 2)
      This newspaper features a cover story on the closing of The Onyx Cafe.
    - Los Angeles Reader, v. 16, no. 23. Los Angeles., 1994 March 18 (Box 193, Folder 9)
    - Los Angeles Reader, v. 16, no. 25. Los Angeles., 1994 April 1 (Box 193, Folder 9)
    - Los Angeles Theatres, v. 1, no. 9. Los Angeles., 1993 September 30-October 14 (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - Los Angeles Times. Los Angeles., 1981 January 18 (Box 132, Folder 4)
      This folder contains a clipping of Yoko Ono's "In Gratitude" letter and a copy of "A Love Letter From John And Yoko To People Who Ask Us What, When, And Why."
    - Los Angeles Times. Los Angeles., 1997 April 6 (Box 153, Folder 6)
      The death of Allen Ginsberg is featured on the front page.
    - Los Angeles Times. Los Angeles., 2013 November 24 (Box 153, Folder 7)
      The death of Wanda Coleman is featured on the front page.
    - Los Angeles Times Magazine. Los Angeles., 1987 March 22 (Box 132, Folder 5)
      This issue includes a feature on Charles Bukowski.
    - Lost Glove, v. 1, no. 1. Cambridge., 1977 (Box 343, Folder 8)
    - Louis Stern Fine Arts. West Hollywood., 1999 (Box 132, Folder 6)
      This is a catalog for Pol Bury: Fountains and Other Intriguing Works.
    - Love Works. Los Angeles., 1998 Summer (Box 132, Folder 7)
    - Lummox Journal, v. 1-2. San Pedro., 1995 November (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - Lummox Journal, v. 3-4. San Pedro., 1997 April (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - Lummox Journal, v. 5, no. 8. San Pedro., 1999 August (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - Lummox Journal, v. 5, no. 7. San Pedro., 1999 September (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - Lummox Journal, v. 6, no. 4. San Pedro., 2000 April (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - Lummox Journal, v. 6, no. 8. San Pedro., 2000 August (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - Lummox Journal, v. 7, no. 3. San Pedro., 2001 March (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - Lummox Journal, v. 8, no. 7. San Pedro., 2002 July (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - Lummox Journal, v. 12, no. 1. San Pedro., 2006 January/February (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - Lummox Journal, v. 12, no. 6. San Pedro., 2006 November/December (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - Mad Blood, no. 3. Evergreen., 2004 June (Box 132, Folder 9)
      Griffin's collage, Wash Before Using is on the cover and five more collages are featured inside.
    - Mad Blood, no. 5. Evergreen., 2006 August (Box 132, Folder 9)
    - Magazine, v. 13, no. 1. Venice., 1983 Winter (Box 132, Folder 10)
      This is a publication of the Beyond Baroque Foundation.
    - Magazine, v. 14, no. 1. Venice., 1983/1984 Winter (Box 132, Folder 10)
    - A Magazine Of Paragraphs, v. 1, no. 3. Holyoke., 1987 Winter (Box 132, Folder 11)
    - Maintenant, no. 4. New York., 2010 Spring (Box 132, Folder 12)
    - Malpais Review, v. 2, no. 3. Placitas., 2011-2012 Winter (Box 132, Folder 13)
    - Malpais Review, v. 2, no. 4. Placitas., 2012 Spring (Box 132, Folder 14)
    - Malpais Review, v. 3, no. 2. Placitas., 2012 Autumn (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Malpais Review, v. 3, no. 3. Placitas., 2012-2013 Winter (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - Malpais Review, v. 4, no. 3. Placitas., 2013-2014 Winter (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - Malpais Review, v. 5, no. 4. Placitas., 2015 (Box 343, Folder 9)
    - Malpais Review, v. 6, no. 1. Placitas., 2015 (Box 343, Folder 9)
    - Malpais Review, v. 6, no. 2. Placitas., 2015 (Box 344, Folder 1)
    - Mano-Mano/2. Denver., 1971 July (Box 133, Folder 4)
      This is issue no. 10 of Bowery Press and is dedicated to Kenneth Patchen.
    - Manroot, no. 6/7. San Francisco., 1972 April (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - Marc Snyder: In Black and White. North Canton., 2005 October 24-November 12 (Box 133, Folder 6)
      This catalog is from Snyder's exhibition at the Kent State University Stark Main Hall Gallery.
    - Martin the Satanic Racoon, no. 2. Hollywood., 1999 (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - The Mas Tequila Review, no. 8. Albuquerque., 2014 Winter (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - The Mask Returns, no. 1. Milwaukie., 1992 October (Box 133, Folder 9)
    - The Match! no. 89. Tucson., 1994 Summer (Box 133, Folder 10)
      This anarchist journal's cover headline reads, "Situation -- Hopeless."
    - Memoirs of the Coffee Shop Society, v. 1. Costa Mesa., 1989 January (Box 133, Folder 11)
      These written words by Steven La Ponsie are presented by Bacon and Eggs Publishing.
    - The Mercury Reader, no. 1. Denver., 2002 May (Box 133, Folder 12)
      This is a sample issue with a note on the inside cover from the secret 6.
      The Mercury Reader is a collective endeavor by The Denver Poets Guild to promote, present and preserve the poetry and art of Denver.
    - The Mercury Reader, no. 3. Denver., 2002 July (Box 133, Folder 12)
      This issue and those thereafter are marked as "a denver poet guild/temple of man production."
      This inside cover of this issue features a reproduction of a cartoon of Jimmy Morris, Tony Scibella, Steve Wilson and Stuart Perkoff at the Ogden Bookstore by John Fish, 1971. The inside cover also includes a letter from the gang of 5.
    - The Mercury Reader, no. 4. Denver., 2002 (Box 133, Folder 12)
      This is the slam issue.
    - The Mercury Reader, no. 5. Denver., 2002 August (Box 133, Folder 12)
      This is the Denver Poet's Day issue.
    - The Mercury Reader, no. 6. Denver., 2002 Sept (Box 133, Folder 12)
      This issue is edited by Stan Astrovsky and the inside cover features a black ace and a letter from the gang of 4. The black ace appears on all issues hereafter.
    - The Mercury Reader, no. 7. Denver., 2002 October (Box 133, Folder 12)
      This poetry seance issue is edited by Wally Mason and features poems of or to dead persons.
    - The Mercury Reader, no. 8. Denver., 2002 November (Box 133, Folder 12)
      This issue features a photo of Wanda Witwiky's colt named Black Ace in the winner's circle after winning the three year old championship at Centennial Race Course.
    - The Mercury Reader, no. 10. Denver., 2003 August (Box 133, Folder 12)
      This is the Poet's Day issue.
    - The Mercury Reader, no. 14. Denver., 2004 June (Box 133, Folder 12)
      This is a Mermaid Springs Special Edition.
    - The Mercury Reader. Denver., 2003 Halloween (Box 133, Folder 12)
      This is the Poetry Seance Issue.
    - The Mercury Reader. Denver., 2003 November (Box 133, Folder 12)
      This is the Tony Scibella Memorial Issue. Griffin's Lady broadside is printed on neon green paper and inserted in the center of this publication.
    - Metro Bookmark. Los Angeles., 1997 April (Box 134, Folder 1)
      These series includes the following poets: Sesshu Foster, Adrienne Su, Patty Sue Jones, Laura Stickney, J. Raul Plasencia, Leo Padilla, Terry Wolverton, Ruben Martinez, and Janet Sternburg.
      This series of seven bookmarks was commissioned by the Metropolitan Transportation Authority to celebrate National Poetry Month and encourage people to use Metro Bus and Metro Rail when traveling to their public libraries. This set was sent to Griffin by Eric Brown.
    - Mezzotints By Sir Frank Short. London., 1974 February 14-March 1 (Box 134, Folder 2)
      This is the catalog for the Mezzotints by Sir Frank Short after Four Paintings by G.F. Watts exhibition at Hartnoll & Eyre.
    - MICA, no. 3. Santa Barbara., 1961 June (Box 134, Folder 3)
      This issue was edited and published by Helmut Bonheim and Raymond Federman.
    - The Mile High Underground, v. 1, no. 6. Denver., 1967 Fall (Box 134, Folder 4)
      This issue is edited by James Ryan Morris. The cover design is by Tony Scibella.
    - Miscellaneous Man, v. 1, no. 1. Los Angeles., 1968 Summer (Box 134, Folder 5)
      The New Los Angeles Quarterly of Literature & Art is edited by William J. Margolis with Associate Editor Tony Scibella. The Miscellaneous MANifesto is printed on the inside cover with a dedication to The Lady. The table of contents is signed by contributor John Thomas, 1968.
    - MOCA Cleveland. Cleveland. Santa Monica., 2003 (Box 134, Folder 6)
      This catalogue for the Yoshitomo Nara: Nothing Ever Happens exhibition was published by the Museum of Contemporary Art Cleveland and Perceval Press, Los Angeles. Contributors include Billie Joe Armstrong, Carrie Brownstein, John Doe, Leonard Nimoy, and Deborah Harry.
    - Modern Man, v. 11, no. 3-123. Skokie., 1961 September (Box 134, Folder 7)
      An article on Venice West appears on page 38.
    - The Moment, no. 2. Woodland Hills., 1987 March (Box 134, Folder 8)
      The masthead describes this publication edited by Chris Behling, Kevin Bartnof and Eric Lyden as "A Randomly Published L.A. Journal Of The Arts."
      This Gonzo type Los Angeles DIY Xerox poetry/lit zine from the late 1980s-mid 1990s was edited and published by San Fernando Valley poets Kevin Bartnof, Chris Behling and Eric Lyden. Like Shattersheet just before it, The Moment included listings of venues and readings. When Griffin met editor Eric Lyden at a Poeccentric Lounge reading in downtown L.A., Lyden recruited him to submit poetry and Griffin then volunteered to work on staff doing whatever was needed.
    - The Moment, no. 4. Woodland Hills., 1987 July (Box 134, Folder 8)
      This issue focuses on L.A.'s homeless population.
    - The Moment, no. 5. Woodland Hills., 1987 November (Box 134, Folder 8)
    - The Moment, no. 6. Woodland Hills., 1988 Spring (Box 134, Folder 8)
      This issue features Henry Rollins "one tough guy" on the cover.
    - Momentum, v. 1, no. 1. Los Angeles., 1974 March (Box 134, Folder 9)
      This issue published by Century City Educational Arts Project includes work by Linda King, Lee Mallory, and William Mohr.
    - Monterey Poetry Review, v. 1, no. 2. Santa Cruz., 2005 Summer (Box 134, Folder 10)
    - Moody Street Irregulars, no. 15. Clarence Center., 1985 Spring (Box 134, Folder 11)
      This is the Music Issue II of this Jack Kerouac newsletter.
    - Moody Street Irregulars, no. 16-17. Clarence Center., 1986 Summer (Box 134, Folder 11)
      This is the On the Road Issue of this Jack Kerouac newsletter.
    - Moody Street Irregulars, no. 18-19. Clarence Center., 1987 Fall (Box 134, Folder 11)
      This is the Ketchup Too! Issue of this Jack Kerouac newsletter.
    - Moody Street Irregulars, no. 20-21. Clarence Center., 1989 Spring (Box 134, Folder 11)
      This is the 10th Anniversary Memorial Issue of this Jack Kerouac newsletter with tributes for George Montgomery, John Clellon Holmes, Jack Kerouac, and Ed Chaput. This folder also contains correspondence from Editor Joy Walsh to Griffin.
    - Moody Street Irregulars, no. 27. Clarence Center., 1992 Spring (Box 134, Folder 11)
      This "Special Poetry Issue" features Visions of Kerouac on the cover.
    - Moravagine 2, no. 4. Denver., 1984 (Box 134, Folder 12)
      This issue is edited by John Macker.
    - Mountain Cat, no. 2. Denver., 1980 (Box 134, Folder 13)
      This issue is edited by Jess Graf.
    - Mouseion, no. 4. Bournemouth., 2005 May (Box 134, Folder 14)
    - Mr. Kite's Leaf, v. 1, no. 1. Pacific Palisades., 1988 February 29 (Box 134, Folder 15)
      The Lost Tribe and The Ringling Sisters are previewed as upcoming shows at the Hippodrome.
    - The Museum of Modern Art Bulletin, v. 25, no. 1. New York., 1957 (Box 134, Folder 16)
      This bulletin is for sculptor David Smith's exhibition at the MOMA.
    - The Musophobist, v. 1, no. 1. Tilton., 2012 May 6 (Box 134, Folder 17)
    - MUST, no. 1. Painted Post., 2009 (Box 134, Folder 18)
    - MUST, no. 2. Painted Post., 2009 (Box 134, Folder 18)
    - MUST, no. 3. Painted Post., 2009 (Box 134, Folder 18)